

fr:

  nav:
    utility:
      about: "f-About"
      help: "f-help"
      contact: "f-Contact"
      sign_in: "f-Sign In"
    main:
      content:
        title: "f-Content"
        items:
          country: "f-Country"
          water: "f-Water"
          population: "f-Population"
      cost:
        title: "f-Cost Data"
        items:
          capital: "f-Capital Expenditure"
          recurrent: "f-Recurrent Expenditure"
      service:
        title: "f-Service"
        items:
          time: "f-Time"
          quantity: "f-Quantity"
          quality: "f-Quality"
          reliability: "f-Reliability"

  buttons:
    next: "f-Next"
    start: "f-OK! Start using the calculator"
    save: "f-Save"

  inputs:
    choose_a_country: "f-Choose a country"

  form:
    skip: "f-skip this question"
    shared:
      country:
        question: "f-In which country does your programme (intervention) take place?"
      capital:
          question: "f-What is the capital expenditure to set up the water service per person?"
      recurrent:
          question: "f-What is the recurrent expenditure to operate, maintain and support service delivery per person per year?"
          value_label: "f-Per person<br/> per year"
    water_basic:
      water:
        question: "f-What is the main water source use to provide water?"
        answers:
          a0: "f-Borehole & Handpump"
          a1: "f-Mechanised "
          a2: "f-Single-Town"
          a3: "f-Multi-Town1"
          a4: "f-Multi-Town2"
      population:
        question: "f-How many people live in the area of intervention?"
        value_label: "f-People"
        answers:
          a0: "f-Less than 500"
          a1: "f-Between 501 and 5,000"
          a2: "f-Between 5,001 and 15,000"
          a3: "f-More than 15,000"
      time:
        question: "f-How long does water collection take per day from the formal sources?"
        value_label: "f-Minutes per day"
        answers:
          a0:  "Less than 10"
          a1: "f-Between 10 and 30"
          a2: "f-Between 30 and 60"
          a3: "f-More than 60"
      quantity:
        question: "f-What is the actual use of water from formal sources? (Litres per person per day)"
        value_label: "f-Per person<br/> per day"
        answers:
          a0: "f-Less than 5 liters"
          a1: "f-Between 5 and 20 liters"
          a2: "f-Between 21-60 liters"
          a3: "f-More than 60 liters"
      quality:
        question: "f-Is water quality testing done?"
        answers:
          a0: "f-No testing"
          a1: "f-One-off test after construction"
          a2: "f-Occasional and meets standards"
          a3: "f-Regular and meets standards"
      reliability:
        question: "f-How reliable is the service? How many days per year is the water system not working?"
        answers:
          a0: "f-Works all the time"
          a1: "f-Works most of the days, but not &gt; 12 days"
          a2: "f-Many break-downs slow repairs"
          a3: "f-Not working"
    sanitation_basic:
      household:
        question: "f-What is the typical household size?"
      latrine:
        question: "f-What is the main improved water source used to provide water?"
        answers:
          a0: "f-Traditional pit latrine"
          a1: "f-Trad. improved pit latrine"
          a2: "f-Slab latrine"
          a3: "f-Vip latrine"
          a4: "f-Pour Flush Latrine"
          a5: "f-Latrine with septic tank"
      providing:
        question: "f-Does the delivery model provide latrines at the household level?"
        answers:
          a0: "f-Yes"
          a1: "f-No"
      impermeability:
        question: "f-Does the latrine have an impermeable slab?"
        answers:
          a0: "f-Impermeable slab"
          a1: "f-Not impermeable slab"
      environment:
        question: "f-What is the environmental impact of the delivery model?"
        answers:
          a0: "f-Non problematic +safe disposal +re-usability"
          a1: "f-Non problematic +safe disposal"
          a2: "f-Significant pollution"
      usage:
        question: "f-Which family members use the latrine?"
        answers:
          a0: "f-All"
          a1: "f-Some"
          a2: "f-None"
      reliability:
        question: "f-Is the latrine cleaned and emptied?"
        answers:
          a0: "f-Yes"
          a1: "f-Unreliable"
          a2: "f-Not"

  footer:
    final_report: "f-Final Reports"
    complete: "f-Complete"